#### Contact

arnaud@citytaps.org

www.linkedin.com/in/arnaud-brunelle-48b4aa (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Business Development Product Management Product Marketing

#### Languages

English (Full Professional)
Chinese (Elementary)
French (Native or Bilingual)

# **Arnaud Brunelle**

☆Chief Commercial Officer☆B2B & B2G☆running water in every urban home

Greater Paris Metropolitan Region

# Summary

Seasoned sales manager in B2B and B2G. Specialized in offering and supporting implementation of complex solutions (hardware +software+service). Experiences across multiple geographies (Europe, Asia, Africa).

Skills : Sales management, Marketing, Business development Passionate about water conservation, energy efficiency, IoT

# Experience

CityTaps
Chief Commercial Officer
March 2018 - Present (3 years 8 months)
Paris Area, France

#### Itron

10 years 9 months

Sales Director - Central Europe, Scandinavia, Mediterranean countries May 2010 - February 2018 (7 years 10 months)

Paris Area, France

Business Development Manager January 2010 - April 2010 (4 months)

Strategic marketing manager
June 2007 - January 2010 (2 years 8 months)

Actaris Metering Systems 4 years 10 months

Regional Sales Manager - China January 2005 - May 2007 (2 years 5 months)

Marketing Manager - Asia August 2002 - December 2004 (2 years 5 months) Page 1 of 2 Schlumberger Product Manager August 1999 - July 2002 (3 years)

Thomson Electron Tubes
Assistant to Production Manager
January 1998 - June 1999 (1 year 6 months)

### Education

Arts et Métiers ParisTech - École Nationale Supérieure d'Arts et Métiers

Master's Degree, Management, Manufacturing, Engineering · (1994 - 1997)